交差するV・S　奪い合う空間
A crossing V・S a scrambling space
飛び交うbooing&amp;yell　高まる　Let's stand up!
Fly, booing&amp;yell, rise. Let’s stand up!
分つ勝・敗が舞う　drawならもう一回
The victory splitted ・ the defeat dances; if you draw one more time
最高のshowにhighがMax　高鳴る fight!!
In the best show the high throbs at its Max fight!!
熱気にヤラれ浮くファンキーなルージュ
A funky rouge floating in the heat
WonderにWanderer　流星に乗せてエントリー
Wanderer in the Wonder, making the entry on a meteor
世界線突破が開戦のサイン
Breaking through the world’s line is the sign of the war outbreak
早く上がっておいでよ　I on my way
Quickly, go up! I on my way
オリエンタルなエレメンタル煌々
A brilliant, oriental elemental
飼い慣らした情熱　解き放つ魂
Taming the passion, releasing the soul
今　フォークロア轟くヴォークライ
Now, the folklore is roaring, my war cry
迷う事なく　Max bet, All in
I won’t hesitate. Max bet, All in
手と手合わせて　空に踊るFreeの快感
We hold our hands as we dance in the sky, feeling free
ゴメンね　大人にはまだなれない
I’m sorry, I still haven’t become an adult
真っすぐに　ひたすらに
Always ahead, determined
ありのままに　あるがままに
As you are, as we are
行こう　飛び出して
Let’s go, jump!
すべて夢のまた夢で見た夢ならば
If all I dream of is but a dream within a dream
ココロ無傷じゃもういられないnight
My heart won’t be hurt anymore in the night
だったら　瞬く星も私のモノ
If that’s so, the twinkle stars will be mine
楽しんだもん勝ち
It’s the joy of victory
また巡り会えたらキミに　伝えたい言葉
If I’ll ever meet you again, there’s a word I want to tell
ときめく　目くるめく　色鮮やかな世界
This throbbing, dazzling, vivid world
魅せたくて　瞳の奥のマテリアル
Could confuse the material inside your eyes
きらびやかに　闇に踊る
Dance gorgeously in the night
すべて　真夏の夜の夢
It is all a midsummer night’s dream
魔法少女も流行り廃り
Even the magical girls change
呪文無しでもカード1枚でillusion
And without spells, 1 card, illusion
勇気が力になる、とか
Courage will come in hand, or something
You just don't get it, そこは愛でしょー
You just don’t get it, that’s love
目と目合わせて　"イエス"か"はい"で答えなさい
We look into each other’s eyes, please say a “Yes” or “Okay”
ゴメンね　Sickも八苦もお呼びじゃない！
I’m sorry, I never asked to be sick or for the eight suffering!
内緒がいい　秘密がいい
It’s fine to have a secret, some secrets
私達と　貴方だけの
Our and yours only
魔法　解けないで
Magic that can’t be broken
いつも裏のその裏は表じゃなくて
Always at the depths’ bottom, where there’s no surface
月も真ん丸じゃもういられないnight
Even the full moon there’s no more in the night
だったら　キミの涙も私のモノ
If that’s so, your tears will be mine
悲しんじゃ損だし
It’s the sadness of defeated
また大切なこの時を　越えて届けたい
I want to go through and give you this important time
何度でも　何回でも　茜に染まる世界
Many times, again and again, the world is tainted in madder
追いかけて　記憶の底のアルカナ
As I pursue the arcana at the bottom of my memories
オリジナルの　闇に沈む
I sink into the original darkness
すべて　真冬の夜の夢
It is all a midwinter night’s dream
もう隠せない　コノキモチニ、ウソハツケナイ
You can’t hide anymore, from those feeling, don’t lie
ゴメンね　悪いコでも構わない
I’m sorry, it doesn’t matter if you’re a bad guy
聴こえてる？　教えてRune
Are you listening? Tell me the Rune
このままでいい？　退屈なDay
It’s fine like this? It’s a boring day
make up　今すぐ　Area-ZEROから始めよう
make up right now, let’s start from the Area-ZERO
いつか夢をまた夢に変える日までは
One day, dreams will become dreams. Until that day
覚めない　恋心激しいMagus night
Don’t wake up, my beloved, forceful Magus night
だったら　キミの隣も私のモノ
If that’s so, all around you will be mine
最後は正義の勝ち
In the end, justice wins
また巡り会うからキミと　この空の上で
When I’ll meet you again, above this sky
ときめく　目くるめく　色鮮やかな世界
This throbbing, dazzling, vivid world
捕まえて　瞳の奥のメモリア
Will be caught as a memory inside your eyes
きらびやかに　闇に踊る
Dance gorgeously in the night
すべて　真夏の夜の夢
It is all a midsummer night’s dream
踊れ　すべて　ただ胡蝶の夢
Dance, everything is just the dream of a butterfly